in this tutorial I'll be using path
在本教程中，我将使用路径
effects and inkscape to show you how you
Effects和Inkscape向您展示如何
can add these decorative elements to
可以将这些装饰元素添加到
your text known as swashes and to follow
你的文字被称为花式和跟随式
along with what I'm doing here you'll
加上我在这里做的事，你会发现
need to download and install this font
需要下载并安装此字体
which I will have Linked In the
我会将其链接到
description below so let's get started
下面的描述，让我们开始吧
uh I'm going to grab my text tool and
我要拿起我的文本工具
I'm going to write on the canvas swashes
我要在帆布花纹上写字
just for this demonstration and I'm
只是为了这个演示，而我是
going to open up my text editor so let
我要打开我的文本编辑器，让
me grab my text menu and I'm going to
我拿起我的文本菜单，我要
look for that font that I already have
寻找我已经拥有的字体
installed click apply
已安装，请单击应用
and I'm going to scale this up a little
我要把这个放大一点
bit I'm going to hold control while I'm
我要控制自己，而我是
doing that so that it locks the
这样做的目的是锁定
proportions and preserves the aspect
比例和保留纵横比
ratio and what I will do now is I will
我现在要做的是我会
convert this to a path so I'll go I will
把它转换成一条路径，这样我就会走，我会
go to path object to path and I'll split
转到路径对象到路径，我将拆分
the letters apart so I will go to path
字母分开，所以我要去PATH
and choose split
并选择拆分
path and now it is individual letters so
路径，现在它是单个字母，所以
what I'm going to do is I'm going to use
我要做的是我要用
the pencil tool to manually draw lines
用于手动绘制线条的铅笔工具
coming off of these letters here to show
从这些信件中脱颖而出来展示
you what I mean uh I was able to draw a
你什么意思，我的意思是，呃，我能够画一个
line that comes off the top of this
从这上面下来的那条线
letter H and swoops underneath like that
字母H，然后像这样在下面猛扑
uh we can do that with the pencil tool
呃，我们可以用铅笔工具来做
by just drawing a regular plain line and
只需画一条普通的线条
then we're going to use path effects to
然后我们将使用路径效果来
make the line look like it's consistent
让这条线看起来是一致的
with the style of the text so I'm going
对文本的风格，所以我要
to grab the P the pencil tool over here
在这里拿起铅笔工具
you can access it by pressing the letter
您可以通过按字母来访问它
P on the keyboard I'm going to use the
我将使用键盘上的P键
regular mode the standard uh regular
常规模式，标准的，呃常规的
mode for this what I'm doing here and
我在这里所做的一切的模式
then over here where it says smoothing
然后在这里，上面写着平滑
I'm going to set that to 50 for now you
现在我要把它设置为50
may have to adjust this based on the
可能需要根据
size of your text on your screen so I'm
你屏幕上的文字大小，所以我
going to start with those settings and
我们将从这些设置开始，
I'm just going to click and drag to draw
我只需点击并拖动即可绘制
a line like this that swoops around and
像这样的一条线，突然出现在
goes under the text like that and what
像这样放在正文下面什么的
you can do now is you can grab your
你现在能做的就是拿起你的
nodes tool and adjust to these nodes so
节点工具并根据这些节点进行调整，以便
that it looks a little more smooth you
让你看起来更顺滑一点
may have to delete nodes if you have too
可能需要删除节点，如果您也有
many of them if you drew like a very
他们中的许多人如果你画得像一个非常
shaky line uh like the fewer nodes you
摇摇晃晃的线，就像你的节点越少
have the smoother of a line you get so
有一条更流畅的线，你就是这样
I'm going to try deleting some of these
我要试着删除其中的一些
nodes and seeing if that gives me a
节点，看看这是否给了我一个
better result so I'm just going to
更好的结果，所以我要
adjust this a little bit
把这个稍微调一下
and the idea here is that you want this
这里的想法是，你想要这个
line going consistent with the direction
与方向一致的直线
of this part of the letter H so you want
字母H的这一部分，所以你想
this to be nice and consistent so let me
这是好的和一致的，所以让我
adjust this a little
把这个稍微调一下
more and I'm happy with how that looks
更多，我对它的样子很满意
what I'm going to do now is I'm going to
我现在要做的是我要
adjust this a little bit so I'll grab my
稍微调整一下，这样我就可以拿起我的
selection tool I'm going to move this up
选择工具，我要将这个向上移动
a little bit and I may even rotate this
一点点，我甚至可能会旋转这个
around a tiny bit as well just so it has
也只有一点点，所以它已经
more of a uh consistent Direction there
更多的是呃一致的方向
and now what I'm going to do is I'm
现在我要做的是
going to grab the power stroke path
要抓住力量划水路径
effects let me open up my path effects
特效让我打开我的路径特效
menu by going to path and selecting path
通过转到路径并选择路径来选择菜单
effects and I'm going to look for Power
效果和我要寻找的力量
Stroke so I'll just type in pwe and
笔划，所以我只需输入Pwe和
there it is right there power stroke and
就在那里，动力冲程和
with power stroke applied I can grab my
用力划水后，我可以抓起我的
nodes tool and you'll see these pink
结点工具，您将看到这些粉色
handles now on the path once you apply
一旦您申请，现在路径上的句柄
the power stroke and you can use these
动力冲程，你可以使用这些
pink handles to change the width of the
粉色手柄可更改
line at that particular point so I'm
在那个特定的点上划线，所以我
going to make this line a little more
我要把这一行做得更多一点
consistent with this part of the letter
与信中的这一部分一致
H if you notice here there's a little
如果你注意到这里有一点
bit of a like a little bit of a corner a
有点像一个小角落
little bit of a dip don't worry about
稍有下降，别担心
that we're going to go correct that
我们要改正这一点
later we're just looking to get a
稍后我们只想得到一个
general consistency here I'm going to
在这里大体一致，我将
take this node and change this as well
获取此节点并同时更改此节点
you may notice that when you're doing
你可能会注意到，当你在做
this you end up with like this sort of
你最终会得到这样的结果
effect right here if you're doing that
如果你这样做，就会在这里产生效果
then just move the node or move the
然后只需移动节点或移动
handle back to the other side of the
句柄返回到
line and you should have a better result
行，你应该有一个更好的结果
and I'm going to take this one and bring
我要把这张照片带到
this one out like that or I may have to
这一张是这样的，否则我可能不得不
bring this one
把这件拿来
up and I'll adjust this a little bit
向上，我会稍微调整一下这个
and the good thing about this is that
这件事的好处是
you can change the direction of your uh
你可以改变你的这个方向
nodes still while you're doing this so
当您执行此操作时，节点仍处于静止状态
nothing is finalized just yet so let me
一切都还没有敲定，所以让我
zoom out and see how this looks in
缩小并查看放大后的效果
comparison um you want to make the the
比较，嗯，你想做的是
uh weight of the swashes consistent with
呃，水花的重量与
the weight of the letters so I noticed
信件的重量，所以我注意到了
this is a little too little too heavy so
这个有点太小太重了，所以
I'll bring that down a little
我会把价格降低一点。
bit there we go I like how that looks
我们走吧，我喜欢它的样子
right
正确的
there and I'm going to grab my selection
好了，我要拿起我的选择
tool now and I'm just going to to change
工具现在，我只是要更改
the position of this a little more I may
这一立场我可能会再多一点
want to rotate this around just a little
我想把这个旋转一下
more just to match the direction of that
更多的只是为了配合这个方向
letter and I'll bring this down some a
一封信，我会把这个写下来
little
一点儿
bit and that looks pretty good I think
有点，我觉得这看起来很不错
I'm going to leave that just as it is
我要让它保持原样
and I'm going to come over here and draw
我要到这里来抽签
another one now so let me come over here
现在又来了一个，所以让我来这里
to my pencil tool and again I'm going to
我的铅笔工具，我要再一次
follow the the direction of the letter
顺着信的方向走
and just draw my line you may have to
只要画出我的底线，你可能就得
try a couple of times cuz I just messed
试几次，因为我刚刚搞砸了
that one up right there I'm going to
就在那上面，我要去
press command Z or control Z to undo
按命令Z或Ctrl Z撤消
that and try again
然后重试
okay that one's a little better I'm
好的，这个好一点，我是
going to grab my nodes tool now and I'm
现在我要拿起我的节点工具，我
going to delete some of these extra
我要删除其中一些多余的内容
nodes in here like I don't need this one
节点在这里，就像我不需要这个
oops let me try that again I don't need
哦，让我再试一次，我不需要
that
那
one and I'm going to adjust these ones a
一个，我要把这几个调整成
little
一点儿
bit okay so I think that's looking a lot
有点好，所以我认为这看起来很多
better now like I mentioned earlier the
现在更好了，就像我前面提到的那样
fewer nodes you have the smoother the
您拥有的节点越少，
line is so you want to have as few nodes
线是这样的，所以你想要有尽可能少的节点
in there as possible so now that that's
尽可能在那里，所以现在这是
done let me go to back to my uh path
做完了，让我回到我的呃道路上
effects and I'm going to apply another
效果，我将应用另一个
power
电源
stroke and now I can grab my nodes tool
笔划，现在我可以抓起我的节点工具
and adjust the size of the uh or adjust
并调整呃的大小或调整
the weight of the
它的重量
line okay so let me grab my selection
好的，让我拿出我的选择
tool now and position this I'll put this
工具，把这个放好，我会把这个
up a little
往上一点
more there we go that looks a lot better
我们去的更多，看起来好多了
and one final touch I'll add here is
我要在这里补充的最后一点是
I'll add another swash to the letter W
我会在字母W后面再加一个花环
so let me repeat that same process I'm
所以让我重复同样的过程，我正在
going to grab my pencil tool I'll just
去拿我的铅笔工具，我就
press the letter P on the keyboard draw
按键盘上的字母P绘制
my
我的
line and now I will just reposition this
现在我要把这个重新定位
one as well okay so let's address the um
一个也行，好的，让我们来谈谈这个
these little Corners that show up these
这些小角落展现了这些
little inconsistencies where the swashes
一些不一致的地方，花瓶
connect with the letters to fix that
用字母连接来修复它
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
我要做的是我要
select the swash and then I'm going to
选择花边，然后我要
hold shift and select the letter and I'm
按住Shift键并选择字母，然后我
just going to unify them together before
只是要把它们统一在一起之前
I do that though I do have to warn you
我确实这么做了，但我必须警告你
that once you do this this effect will
一旦你这样做了，这个效果就会
be finalized and this will become a
最终敲定，这将成为
regular path you won't be able to change
您将无法更改常规路径
the consistency or the the weight of the
粘稠度或重量
line or the direction of it anymore
线条还是它的方向？
without editing the nodes uh so just to
不编辑节点，呃，只是为了
warn you there make sure everything
警告你一定要确保一切
looks good before you do this next step
在你做下一步之前看起来不错
and then go to path
然后转到Path
Union and now what I'm going to do to
联合，现在我要做的是
smooth this out I'm just going to grab
把这件事解决掉我要去拿
my nodes tool and I'll just go in there
我的节点工具，然后我就进去了
and delete those nodes and when you
并删除这些节点，并且当您
delete those nodes you can take these
删除那些节点，您可以使用这些
handles and straighten them out and you
把手，把它们弄直，然后你
have a nice a nice smooth line there so
有一条漂亮的流畅的线条，所以
let me do the same thing over here I'll
让我在这里做同样的事情，我会
delete these nodes and now we have a
删除这些节点，现在我们就有了一个
nice smooth line and I'll do the same
线条很流畅，我也会这么做的
thing over here I'm going to grab my
这里的东西我要拿起我的
selection tool I'm going to select all
选择工具我要选择全部
of these by holding shift and clicking
通过按住Shift键并单击
on them all three objects go to path
在它们上面，所有三个对象都指向Path
Union and I will do the same thing over
尤尼恩和我也会做同样的事
here I'm going to delete these nodes out
在这里，我将删除这些节点
of here
离开这里
now one final thing I wanted to address
现在我想说的最后一件事
with this design is that if you notice
这个设计是，如果你注意到
the tips of these swashes they end in
在这些挥舞的尖端，他们以
sharp points and that's not consistent
尖锐的观点，这是不一致的
with the rest of these letters these
这些字母的其余部分是
letters for the most part have rounded
大部分字母都是四舍五入的
caps on them so what I'm going to do is
所以我要做的是
I'm going to grab my Eraser and erase
我去拿我的橡皮擦擦掉
the ends of these uh the the ends of
这些的末端，呃末端的末端
these points so there's actually a few
这些点，所以实际上有几个
ways to do this for this I'm just using
做这件事的方法我只是在用
the Eraser I'm going to grab the Eraser
橡皮擦我去拿橡皮擦
tool I'm going to set the width to 20
工具，我要将宽度设置为20
okay let me try that again eraser tool
好的，让我再试一次橡皮擦工具
set the width to
将宽度设置为
20 and I'm just going to erase off part
20，我要把那部分擦掉
of this letter right here like
就像这封信一样
that and now I'm going to grab my nodes
现在我要抓起我的节点
tool I'm going to select these nodes get
工具我要选择这些节点GET
rid of them select all these nodes in
清除它们选择中的所有这些节点
the middle here not the ones on the ends
中间的，不是末端的
just the ones in the middle get rid of
只有中间的人才能去掉
them and then we can take this line or
然后我们可以走这条线或者
take these nodes and pull this out like
把这些节点拿出来，就像这样
that and now we have a rounded cap on
现在我们戴上了一顶圆帽
there like I said there's various ways
就像我说的，有很多种方法
to do this you can draw a bezier path
为此，可以绘制一条贝塞尔曲线路径
and do a path difference and then
做一次路径差分，然后
reshape it this way but this is just the
以这种方式重塑它，但这只是
way I'm doing it for this tutorial I'm
在本教程中，我这样做的方式是
just using the Eraser I'll do the same
只要用橡皮擦，我也会这么做的
thing over here you have to select the
在这里，你必须选择
object first then grab the Eraser and
对象，然后抓起橡皮擦并
then you can draw right through there
然后你就可以在那里画画了
and erase that off so I'll just go
把它擦掉，这样我就走了
through and erase this
穿过并擦除这一切
and there we go that looks a lot more
我们开始了，看起来要多得多
consistent with the rest of the letters
与其他信件一致
so I think that should do it for this
所以我认为这应该可以解决这个问题
tutorial that's how you can take text
教程，这就是你获取文本的方法
and add some decorative elements known
并添加一些已知的装饰元素
as swashes to it using path effects in
使用中的路径效果向它倾斜
inkscape if you found this lesson useful
如果您发现本课有用，inkscape
then consider checking out my inkscape
然后考虑检查我的水墨景观
master class it's a collection of over
大师班这是一个集合
60 videos where I go over all of the
60个视频，我回顾了所有
tools and features in inkscape and I
inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示
how they work kind of like how I did in
他们的工作方式有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人视频
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提问的社区
and get help from me anytime you want
并随时从我这里获得帮助
and best of all there's no monthly
最重要的是没有每月
membership fees you just pay $17 one
会员费只需支付17美元一个
time and you're in for Life I'll have
时间，你将迎来我将拥有的生活
some information about that down below
下面有一些相关信息
if you want to check that out as always
如果您想一如既往地检查一下
thanks for watching
感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]
oh
哦